pinoyexchange.com 2019-12-15

# PinoyExchange.com | Privacy Policy

Last updated: June 18, 2018 

PEX Online Community Corp. ("us", "we", or "our") operates <https://www.pinoyexchange.com/> (the "Site"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site. 

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. 

## Information Collection And Use

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to name, email address, username, facebook photo, and contact number for the purpose of moderating your participation in the forum and for processing promo-related activities including promo claims within the site. 

We may occasionally contact you to obtain feedback on the forum to improve user experience which may include data on your usage habits, preferences and other demographic details such as gender, age among other things. As part of using our platform, we may have to share your contact information with third parties in order to improve your use of our online platform. 

## Information Shared With Third Parties

In addition, as a necessary part of providing the Services, we may disclose information collected from you to certain third parties. For example, we may disclose certain Personal Information about you to our third-party service providers (e.g., our third party website service providers), so long as they are only using the Personal Information to provide services to us. We may also share your information to Advertisers for processing promo-related activities. 

If another company acquires our company, business, or our assets, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by it and us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

Under certain limited circumstances, we may cooperate with legal investigations and/or we may be subject to legal requirements to disclose information collected through the Site or the Services, such as, by way of example, to a court or a governmental agency, and our policy is to provide such cooperation and comply fully with all such legal requirements. 

## Log Data

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site ("Log Data"). 

This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. 

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze the collected data. 

## Communications

For those who have submitted their forms with us or for those who sent in queries, we may use your Personal Information to contact you for any marketing or promotional materials. 

## Cookies

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site. 

## Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

## Data retention

We retain information you provide to us and which we collect about you, including Personal Information and Personal Data, for so long as we continue to provide services to you and specifically until such time as you request us to delete your Personal Information and Personal Data. 

## Data transfers

PEX's corporate headquarter is located in Philippines, and so your information may be transferred to, and/or stored in, Philippines. In addition, we sometimes transfer or disclose information to third parties including to persons and businesses outside Philippines including in the United States of America, and Canada. 

These transfers are made in order to assist us to provide you with the products and services, and/or to improve the products and services we offer you. Where we transfer information to persons outside of Philippines, that information will be treated according to similar (but not lesser) standards imposed by the requirements of the Privacy Act (and where appropriate the GDPR) in relation to that information by PEX's entry into binding contractual arrangements with such third parties. 

## Rights

You hereby acknowledge that you have been informed and are aware of the following rights as a data subject under the Applicable Law: (a) right to object to the collection, processing, use or storage, (b) right to access, correct, and erase or block, any information pertaining to you that is collected, processed, used, stored or disclosed by PEx Online Community Corp, (c) right to file for damages due to false, incomplete, outdated, unlawfully obtained or unauthorized use of personal data, considering any violation of his or her rights and freedoms as a data subject, (d) right to data portability where you can request for electronic copies of your personal information 

You hereby grant your informed consent freely and specifically to PEx Online Community Corp’s sharing or disclosure to any of the following (and, in turn, their collection, processing, use, storage, updating and disclosure), of such information, and, for this purpose, the user expressly waives its rights under the Applicable Law. 

## European Union

If you are a resident of the European Union for the purposes of the GDPR, then in addition to what is set out above, the following applies to you. PEX is a data controller and processor for the purposes of the GDPR and by your consenting to this Privacy Statement PEX is able to processes your Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Statement. 

Our Contact details are set out in the “Contact Us” paragraph below. In providing its services to you, PEX may make use of a number of manual and automated processes using your Personal Data and your activity on our Site as tracked by us, in order to provide more tailored and relevant services to you such as targeted advertising, promotional activities, and as basis for nomination to PEX moderators who are responsible for monitoring forum threads, driving thread discussions and deciding spam/clean content. PEX may also use such data in manual and automated processes aimed at providing more tailored and relevant services to Advertisers, such as your personal profile in case Advertisers may require to give out promotional items and/or when placing an ad on the PEX site 

In addition to your rights set out above, you may: 

  * update or rectify any of the Personal Data that we hold about you. This can be done by accessing the Site, logging in to your account and accessing the ‘Settings’ section 
  * withdraw your consent to PEX’s use of your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Statement by requesting PEX to delete your account. This may delete all your account details that we hold, but not necessarily content which you have posted or threads you have participated in. This can be done by writing an email to [pex-info@pinoyexchange.com](mailto:pex-info@pinoyexchange.com) with the subject ‘PEX Account Deletion’ and indicating your username and the associated email address with the account. Verification of account ownership will made within 48 hours. After confirming account ownership, PEX would then now proceed to delete the account of the user. All content posted by the deleted users will have ‘Deleted User’ as the profile handle to prevent any association with former users.   
The above clause may not apply to spammers, however. ‘Spammers’ defined as members who post linkbaits, repetitive advertising on non-classified section and content which do not add value to the discussion will be immediately deleted by the moderator with the user facing potential ban from the forum 
  * request that PEX   
\- provides you with a copy of the Personal Data PEX holds about you in a portable and machine readable form; or  
\- share your Personal Data with a nominated third party; 

You may request that from us by contacting us using any of the methods set out in the “Contact Us” paragraph below 

Should you have any concerns in relation to PEX’s collection and/or processing of your Personal Data set out above (including the right to complain to the Philippine National Privacy Commissioner), you have the right to complain to a supervisory authority (within the meaning of the GDPR). 

Our representative for the purposes of the GDPR is set out below:   
PEX Online Community Inc.  
4th Floor Zeta Building, Legaspi Village Salcedo Street Makati  
Charlie Hernando  
Email: [pex-info@pinoyexchange.com](mailto:pex-info@pinoyexchange.com)  

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of June 18, 2018 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page. 

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. 

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website. 

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us through [pex-info@pinoyexchange.com](mailto:pex-info@pinoyexchange.com)

Copyright 2018. All Rights Reserved.
